[{"answer": " OK, Amber.  Its time for your review", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " How did I do this year", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": " OK, Amber.  Its time for your review", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Well, let me ask you what you think first.  How do you feel about you", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": " How did I do this year", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": "I feel that Ive done exceptionally well at work this past year.  I had the top sale", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Well, let me ask you what you think first.  How do you feel about you", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " I agree.  The management here, myself included, have been very impresse", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 26, "question": "I feel that Ive done exceptionally well at work this past year.  I had the top sale", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 29, "question": " I agree.  The management here, myself included, have been very impresse", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  We really liked your ideas for the new process of clien", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Thank you.  Its been working very smoothly since we started using it", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Youre welcome.  We really liked your ideas for the new process of clien", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Did you work with a team on designing that", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Thank you.  Its been working very smoothly since we started using it", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " No.  I took it upon myself to start that and worked on it alone", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Did you work with a team on designing that", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Very good.  Now, do you feel that you need improvement in any areas", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 39, "question": " No.  I took it upon myself to start that and worked on it alone", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Well, if I had to improve in any area, I guess its taking on too many projects a", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Very good.  Now, do you feel that you need improvement in any areas", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " That sounds like a very effective way to manage your time and keep focused o", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Well, if I had to improve in any area, I guess its taking on too many projects a", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 50, "question": " That sounds like a very effective way to manage your time and keep focused o", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " You really have exceeded minimum work expectations this review period", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": "   Oh, a 5% raise is not really what I was expecting.  I was expecting a 10", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 55, "question": " You really have exceeded minimum work expectations this review period", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Well, I agree that you have done a great job this past year.  But 10% is a larg", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 59, "question": "   Oh, a 5% raise is not really what I was expecting.  I was expecting a 10", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I did some research on positions similar to mine and found that the averag", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Well, I agree that you have done a great job this past year.  But 10% is a larg", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " I see where youre coming from.  Unfortunately, due to budgetary reasons, w", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 67, "question": " I did some research on positions similar to mine and found that the averag", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": "  I guess that would be OK", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 72, "question": " I see where youre coming from.  Unfortunately, due to budgetary reasons, w", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Most employees only got a 4% raise this year, so 7% is pretty good.  Youre on", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 73, "question": "  I guess that would be OK", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " I appreciate that.  Thank you.  I like working here a lot, so Ill accept the 7%", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Most employees only got a 4% raise this year, so 7% is pretty good.  Youre on", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Great.  Im glad to hear that.  Hopefully, as the budget improves well be able t", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 78, "question": " I appreciate that.  Thank you.  I like working here a lot, so Ill accept the 7%", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Great.  Im glad to hear that.  Hopefully, as the budget improves well be able t", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Well, thats it for the review.  Keep up the excellent work, Amber", "docId": "03-06", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 84}]
